Register of the Price family papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Photographs, 1860-2001. (Box 8, 18)
  Comprised of photographic prints and negatives depicting members of the Price family, friends, and the house and mission in Madagascar. Arranged in chronological order.
  - Prym family, undated. (Box 8)
    Includes photograph of Prym family and photograph of their house in Bonn.
  - Charles Price, undated. (Folder 18: 9)
    Includes images of Price family members, mission in Madagascar, and the Murray family.
  - Hereward Price, 1860-1919. (Folder 18: 10)
    Includes images of Hereward in the army, Siberia, Ernestine Prym, Liese Prym Price, and her home during the war
  - Alexander Alexeiev-Gigh, 1912-1972. (Folder 18: 11)
    Includes images of Alexander Alexeiev-Gigh and Irkutsk in Siberia
  - Kieler Wandervogel, 1918-1933. (Folder 18: 12-13)
    Depicts camping expeditions
  - Book photographs, 1918-1968 (Folder 18: 14)
  - OSS and State Department, circa 1943 (Folder 18: 15)
  - Price family, 1913-2001 (Folder 18: 16)